[
  {
    "question_number": 1,
    "question_text": "Which animal do you like the most?",
    "answer_text": "Eagle",
    "answer_value": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 1,
    "question_text": "Which animal do you like the most?",
    "answer_text": "Lion",
    "answer_value": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 1,
    "question_text": "Which animal do you like the most?",
    "answer_text": "Badger",
    "answer_value": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 1,
    "question_text": "Which animal do you like the most?",
    "answer_text": "Serpent",
    "answer_value": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 2,
    "question_text": "Which attribute do you value most?",
    "answer_text": "Dedication",
    "answer_value": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 2,
    "question_text": "Which attribute do you value most?",
    "answer_text": "Ambition",
    "answer_value": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  2,
    "question_text": "Which attribute do you value most?",
    "answer_text": "Bravery",
    "answer_value": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  2,
    "question_text": "Which attribute do you value most?",
    "answer_text": "Intelligence",
    "answer_value": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  3,
    "question_text": "Which is your favorite color?",
    "answer_text": "Green",
    "answer_value": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  3,
    "question_text": "Which is your favorite color?",
    "answer_text": "Yellow",
    "answer_value": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  3,
    "question_text": "Which is your favorite color?",
    "answer_text": "Blue",
    "answer_value": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question_number":  3,
    "question_text": "Which is your favorite color?",
    "answer_text": "Red",
    "answer_value": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question_text": "Which of the following classic elements do you prefer?",
    "answer_text": "Fire",
    "answer_value": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question_text": "Which of the following classic elements do you prefer?",
    "answer_text": "Air",
    "answer_value": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question_text": "Which of the following classic elements do you prefer?",
    "answer_text": "Water",
    "answer_value": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question_text": "Which of the following classic elements do you prefer?",
    "answer_text": "Earth",
    "answer_value": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question_text": "What is your weakness?",
    "answer_text": "Naivety",
    "answer_value": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question_text": "What is your weakness?",
    "answer_text": "Insecurity",
    "answer_value": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question_text": "What is your weakness?",
    "answer_text": "Arrogance",
    "answer_value": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question_text": "What is your weakness?",
    "answer_text": "Recklessness",
    "answer_value": "Gryffindor"
  }
  ]